<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>Lodestar aims to be a framework that provides directly executable code, unlike most modeling and simulation-centric toolboxes, which have not been tailored for use in real-time applications. At the same time, Lodestar also allows for code generation when performance is particularly important. It comes built-in with many compile-time checks that cover most common typos and bugs (i.e., matrix-vector dimensions mismatch, connecting inputs to inputs, etc.).
To this end, Lodestar adopts a function block description of systems, where each Block provides a pure function (i.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ldstr.dev/docs/prologue/quick-start/</guid><description>Dependencies # CMake A C++11-compliant compiler GiNaC (optional, for resolving algebraic loops) nng (optional, for networking) Building # Simply clone the repository and build using CMake. If you just want to grab a static library, run cmake .. instead of a debug build.
Installing/disabling dependencies You can install the dependencies as follows:
On Ubuntu (Debian): sudo apt-get install libginac-dev libcln-dev libnng-dev On macOS: brew install ginac nng You can disable GiNaC and NNG using the -DWITH_GINAC=OFF -DWITH_NNG=OFF flags when running the cmake command:</description></item></channel></rss>